Finding Aid for Bureau of Government Library (University of Michigan) records, 1935-1980
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Student Papers
  - Nagelberg, Michael L.
    - An Analysis of a Summer Employment Program, 1968. (Box 56)
  - Newton
    - Caro State Hospital -- Budget Request 1960-1961 Instructions for Preparation of Annual Memorandum -- Department of Mental Health Policy Statement (Box 56)
  - Olivo, Alfredo B.
    - An Analysis of the Trends in Municipal Employment of the City of Ann Arbor (FY 1956-67 and FY 1966-67) 1966 (Box 56)
  - Paluka, Joseph
    - Trends in County Finance -- A Study of Seven Counties in Southern Michigan 1961 (Box 56)
  - Perkins, James K.
    - The Role of Interdepartmental Committees in Michigan State Government 1959 (Box 56)
  - Plymouth County Study, 1967. (Box 56)
  - Potash, Stephen J.
    - Michigan Transportation Systems 1963 (Box 56)
  - Potthoff, Edward H.
    - Administration of Personal Property Assessment in Ann Arbor 1950 (Box 56)
  - Precious, Ralph
    - Field Work 375 and 376 Village of Oxford (Box 56)
  - Raymond, Burke M. (Box 57)
    - A Capital Improvements Program for Ann Arbor 1961-1966 (Box 57)
  - Rydland, L.N.
    - Administrative Assistant's Case Problems (Benton Harbor) 1956 (Box 57)
  - Rotche, Phillip J.
    - Manual of Safety and Disciplinary Measures (City of Ann Arbor) 1960 (Box 57)
    - The Administrative Procedures of a Construction Project, Department of Public Works, Ann Arbor 1960 (Box 57)
  - Ryan, John F.
    - Recruitment Activities of the Wayne County Civil Service Commission, circa 1949 (Box 57)
  - Savage, Lawrence C., Jr.
    - Saginaw's City Government: A Manual for High School Students 1953 (Box 57)
  - Sharp, Robert W.
    - Michigan's "First" Legislatures (Box 57)
  - Shogan, Robert
    - Government Public Relations 1952 (Box 57)
  - Smith, Donald Alan
    - Michigan Council -- Manager Charters (Box 57)
  - Smith, Donald V.
    - A Corporate Income Tax for Michigan -- Analysis of the Proposed Tax 1951 (Box 57)
  - Southern, Dodd A.
    - Internship Report, Political Science 591 1961 (Box 57)
  - Spiegelblatt, Henry
    - Charter Provisions for Personnel Administration in Michigan Cities (Box 57)
  - Stark, Lida S.
    - Job Opportunities for the College Graduate Without Experience in the Michigan State Service 1953 (Box 57)
  - Stein, William M.
    - The Stein Report to the Institute: The Case of a Non-Conference Alias Human Relations Inaction in Ann Arbor 1968 (Box 57)
  - Strauss, Dorothee E.
    - A Study of Administrative Organizations of State Departments of Mental Health 1949 (Box 57)
  - Temple, N. M.
    - Municipal Personnel Service -- Wage and Salary Survey 1947 (Box 57)
  - Tomsho, George M.
    - The Federal Field Services in Detroit 1950 (Box 57)
  - Urrutia, Boris
    - Comparative Analysis of Union Contracts in the State of Michigan 1967 (Box 57)
    - The Structure of Government in Ann Arbor 1968 (Box 57)
  - Vamis, John
    - A Population Analysis of Washtenaw County: 1940, 1950 (Box 57)
  - Van der Till, Gordon E.
    - Field Report on Work at the Michigan Municipal League, circa 1966 (Box 57)
  - VanZandt, James
    - Summary and Evaluation of City Hall Internship 1966 (Box 57)
  - Velte, Robin Elizabeth
    - Report of Field Work Experience for public Administration 637 and 638 1966 (Box 57)
  - Williams, Ben A.
    - Michigan Highway Needs -- A Narrative Report 1948 (Box 57)
  - Williams, Wiley J.
    - Administrative Control of State Publications -- the Michigan Experience 1960 (Box 57)
  - Willis, James G.
    - The Role of Assistants to Michigan City Managers, circa 1965 (Box 57)